OBJECTIVE

To work with a progressive organization in which I can contribute my technical skills and experience to improve my own efficiency at the same time achieving the objectives of the organization with the attribute of time, quality and discipline.

EXPERIENCE

HORIZON MOTORS INDIA Pvt Ltd

Jan 2021 - Current date

Sales officer

Main duties performed:-

Meeting customers face to face and holding sales discussions with them

Demonstrating vehicles to customers, including taking them for drives

Educate customers on the features, options, and packages on a range of make and model of vehicles to assist them in making a purchase that fits their needs and budget

Following-up in-bound telephone enquiries, walk in prospects and emails enquiries

Reporting to the vehicle Sales Manager on activities, reviews and analyses

Negotiating the terms of a sales agreement and closing sales

Arranging appointments via Internet Leads

Delivering vehicles to customers

ACE DISTRIBUTORS THIRUVANCHOOR

Jan2020 - Dec 2020

Sales Executive

Main duties performed:

Builds business by identifying and selling prospects; maintaining relationships with clients.

Sells products by establishing contact and developing relationships with prospects; recommending solutions

Prepares reports by collecting, analyzing, and summarizing information

negotiating contracts and packages

demonstrating and presenting products.



SUJITH S

- @ sujithsreekumar0@gmail.com
- **\$590361347**
- Radhamandiram
 Kothala po
 Pampady,kottayam
 kerala 686502

SKILLS

An ability to achieve and exceed targets.

Able to work as part of a busy sales team.

Ability to build a rapport with a wide range of people

Ability to prioritize and meet deadlines on multiple assignments.

Previous related retail experience

A valid driver's license & satisfactory driving record

Unlimited resilience, drive, energy and talent.

Strong leadership, communication and organisational skills

LANGUAGE

English

malayalam

Hindi

Tamil

Arabic

REFERENCE

NISSAN AL ARABIYAH GENUINE SPARE PARTS OMAN

Feb2018 - Nov2019

Sales Executive

Main duties performed:

Help customers find the spare parts they are looking for.

Ensure all necessary parts are stocked and ready for purchase.

Determine replacement parts required, according to inspections of old parts, customer requests, or customers' descriptions of malfunctions.

Sell parts to repair garages, retail, companies, dealers, and the public. Look up stock numbers and prices for parts in catalogs or on computers

Mark and store parts in stockroom according to prearranged system Set up merchandise for display

Answer the customers' questions or problems

Receive and deliver parts to customers

Locate other vendors who have the part if it isn't carried in store.

EDUCATION

AMS COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING NAMAKKAL

2017

BE mechanical engineering

COMPLETED

KITE MARINE TECHNOLOGY KOCHI

2012

Higher diploma program in marine mechanical fitter 80%

PVS HS SCHOOL ALAMPALY

2010

Higher secondary

60%

SVRVNSS HS SCHOOL VAZHOOR

2008

SSLC

69%

Available on request. - ""

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth : 04/11/1991 Marital Status : Married

Nationality : Indian